Guide to the Larry LaRocco Collection 1982-1994
Boise State University Library, Special Collections and Archives
Larry LaRocco Collection
1982-1994
Boise State University Library Special Collections and Archives 1910 University Dr. Boise, Idaho 83725-1430 208-426-3990 archives@boisestate.edu http://library.boisestate.edu/Special/
MSS 139
LaRocco, Larry
approximately 90 linear feet
Chiefly documenting Larry LaRocco's two terms as one of Idaho's two members in the U.S. House of Representatives, 1991-1995.
Larry LaRocco (1946- ) was twice elected to the U.S. House of Representatives from Idaho's 1st District, in 1990 and again in 1992.
The collection includes correspondence, press releases, newsletters, reports, studies, subject files, clippings, photos, tape and video recordings, and other papers, from LaRocco's service in Congress representing the First District of Idaho (North Idaho and the western side of the state); together with campaign and other political papers. Issues represented include wolf reintroduction, salmon recovery, wilderness, national forest and timber policies, forest health, Coeur d'Alene basin cleanup, Snake River Birds of Prey National Conservation Area, and the Persian Gulf War (Operation Desert Storm).
Most of the material within each file is of a secondary nature; there is little correspondence. Although there is little personal correspondence within the general subject files from Washington, the regional offices retained letters and faxes in alphabetical constituent files. Communications between LaRocco and the other members of Congress relating to issues are found within the general files.
The collection is arranged in fourteen series: 1. General files; 2.Campaigns; 3. Washington office; 4. Boise office; 5. Caldwell office; 6. Coeur d'Alene office; 7. Lewiston office; 8. Pre-Congressional; 9. Computer disks; 10. Tape cassettes; 11. Videotapes; 12. Maps; 13. Photos; and 14. Additions. The arrangement of materials within each series is by subject.
Collection is available for research with the exception of select material. Contact Special Collections for additional information.
Gift of Mr. LaRocco, 1995, with subsequent additions.
Idaho--Politics and government--20th century; Legislators--United States--Correspondence; Wildlife recovery--United States; Forest conservation--United States; Birds of prey--Idaho; Morley Nelson Snake River Birds of Prey National Conservation Area (Idaho); Persian Gulf War, 1991--United States; Environmental protection--Idaho--Coeur d'Alene River Watershed; Salmon--Conservation--United States; Wolves--Reintroduction--United States
Idaho; Environmental Activism; Environmental Conditions; Military; Political Campaigns
- General files, 1
  This series consists of general office files, arranged by subject. It shows the breadth of topics LaRocco dealt with during his terms in office.
  - Access to Public Lands, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Land Use; Bureau of Land Management
  - Administrative Housing Proposal, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Housing Proposal: The Bill, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Housing Choice and Community Investment Act; Homeless; Public Housing
  - Africa, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Apartheid; South Africa; Zaire
  - Agency for International Development, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Economic Assistance
  - Agency for International Development, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    University of Idaho; Agriculture; Russia
  - Agriculture, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Agriculture, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    H.R.4554
  - Agriculture: Internal Memos, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Grazing
  - Agriculture: Miscellaneous, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Department of Agriculture; United Dairymen of Idaho; Federal Crop Insurance Corporation
  - Agriculture: Reforms, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Internal Revenue Code; Farmer Retirement Security Act
    H.R.2333
  - Agriculture: Reports, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Farm Bill; Food Safety; Groundwater Quality; GATT
  - Agriculture Department, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Price Supports
  - Agriculture Department: Reorganization, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Department of Agriculture Reorganization Act; Idaho Grain Producers Association
    H.R.3171; S.1970
  - Agriculture Stabilization and Conservation Service, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Rush, Richard
  - Airline Labor Issues, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Airlines--Employees
  - Airline Transporation, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Airlines
  - Alaska North Slope Oil, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Alaska--Oil Production; Department of Commerce
    H.R.2670
  - Alfalfa, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Alyeska Pipeline Service Company, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Oil Spills; Ocean Ecology
  - Alzheimer's Association, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Alzheimer's Disease
  - Amateur Radio Volunteer Service Act, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    H.R.2623
  - America 2000, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Education
  - America 2000: Education Strategy, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Bush, George
  - American Council for Capital Formation, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - American Family Association, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    National Endowment for the Arts
  - American Folklife Center, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    New Jersey; Tourist Trade
  - American Heritage Area Participation Program, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Private Property; Public Lands
    H.R.5044; H.R.3707
  - American Israel Public AFFA Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    International Relations; Jews--Migration
  - American Legion, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - American Nuclear Energy Council, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Nuclear Weapons; Hanford
  - Americans With Disabilities Act, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    H.R.3732
  - Amnesty International, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Human Rights; Capital Punishment; El Salvador; Kuwait; Nicaragua; Iraq
  - Ancient Forest, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Spotted Owl; Old Growth Forest; Forest Reserves
  - Ancient Forest, 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Forest Reserves; Timber Community Economic Adjustment Fund
  - Ancient Forest: Alliance, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Forest Reserves
  - Ancient Forest: Aucoin Bill, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Forest and Community Survival Act; Growth/Forest Planning Bills; Comparison of Bills; Forest Reserves
    Aucoin, Les
    H.R.2807
  - Ancient Forest: Background, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Spotted Owl; Old Growth Forest; Bureau of Land Management; Forest Reserves
  - Ancient Forest: Background, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Old Growth Forest; Fish and Wildlife Service; Forest Reserves
  - Ancient Forest: Chronology, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Old Growth Forest; Forest Reserves
  - Ancient Forest: Conflict, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Old Growth Forest; Defazio/Miller Conflict; Ancient Forest Protection Act; Forest Reserves
    DeFazio, Peter; Miller, George; Vento, Bruce
    H.R.4899
  - Ancient Forest: Correspondence, undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Ancient Forest: Court Decisions, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    Old Growth Forest; Spotted Owl; Forest Reserves
  - Ancient Forest: Environmental Information, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Ancient Forest: Gang of Four Report, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Ancient Forest: Gap Analysis, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    Forest Reserves; Northwest Biodiversity and Community Stability Act
  - Ancient Forest: "God Squad", 1991 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Ancient Forest: Group of Four Report, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Ancient Forest Protection Act; Paper Products; Timber; Forest Reserves
  - Ancient Forest: Group of Four: Miller, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Ancient Forest Protection Act; Forest Reserves
    Miller, Dan
  - Ancient Forest: Habitat, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Salmon; Murrelet; Forest Reserves
  - Ancient Forest: Hearings, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Forest Reserves; Timber Industry
  - Ancient Forest: Housing and Lumber, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Public Lands; Old Growth Forest; Forest Reserves; Timber Industry
    Bethel, James S.
  - Ancient Forest: Huckaby Bill, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Spotted Owl Chronology; Forest Reserves
    H.R.2463
  - Ancient Forest: Industry Information, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Old Growth Forest; Timber Industry; Forest Reserves
  - Ancient Forest: Jobs, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Spotted Owl; American Forestry Association; Timber Industry; Forest Reserves
  - Ancient Forest: Jobs, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Spotted Owl; Labor Management Committee; Timber Industry; Timber--Exports; Forest Reserves
  - Ancient Forest: Jontz and Vento Bills, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Bureau of Land Management; Ancient Forest Reserve System; Ancient Forest Protection Act; Subcommittee Hearing Materials; Forest Reserves
    H.R.1590; H.R.842
  - Ancient Forest: Log Exports, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Log Export Tariffs; Timber Supply; Forest Reserves
  - Ancient Forest: Mark-ups, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Ancient Forest: McDermott's Bill, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Recovery and Ecosystem Conservation Act; Forest Reserves
    McDermott, Jim
    H.R.3432
  - Ancient Forest: Morrison Bill, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Old Growth Forests; Spotted Owl Legislation; Forest Reserves
    H.R.3263
  - Ancient Forest: Preservation Plan, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Spotted Owl; Forest Reserves
  - Ancient Forest: Press, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Critical Habitat; Forest Reserves
  - Ancient Forest: Recovery Plan, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Ancient Forest: Scientific Committee, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Ancient Forest; Old Growth Forest; Forest Reserves
  - Ancient Forest: Specific, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Sierra; Logging Damage; Watershed Protection; Blue Mountains; Forest Reserves
  - Angola, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Animal Damage Control, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Idaho Cattle Association; Bureau of Land Management; Grazing; Agriculture
  - Animal Rights, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Animal Welfare Act; Humane Treatment of Animals; Anti-Live Animal Lure Act; Agriculture
    H.R.3252; H.R.318
  - Annuities Tax, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Taxation
  - Anti-Gay Movement, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Sexuality Education; Citizens for Excellence in Education; Idaho Citizen's Alliance; Homophobia; Human Rights
  - Anti-Gay Proposals, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Idaho Citizen's Alliance; Homophobia; Human Rights
  - Appropriations, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Justice Department; Commerce Department; National Endowment for Democracy; Radio Free Asia; Department of State
    H.R.4603
  - Appropriations, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    Agriculture; Potatoes; Idaho Resource Conservation and Development Association; Poisonous Plant Research Laboratory; Biotechnology
  - Appropriations: Agriculture, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    Wheat; Barley; International Trade
  - Appropriations: Agriculture, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Potatoes
  - Appropriations: Coeur d'Alene Basin, FY95, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Public Lands; Department of Interior Appropriations
  - Appropriations: Coeur d'Alene Tribe, FY95, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Coeur d'Alene Indians; Coeur d'Alene Basin; Department of Interior Appropriations
  - Appropriations: University of Idaho Agricultural Research, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    Agriculture; Biotechnology
  - Appropriations: University of Idaho Biotech, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    Biotechnology
  - Appropriations: University of Idaho College of Agriculture, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Agriculture
  - Archbishop Riordan High School, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Department of Education
  - Arctic National Wildlife Refuge, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    Alaska--Wildlife; Alaska--Natural Resources
  - Arkansas-Idaho Exchange, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    Arkansas--Public Lands; Idaho--Public Lands; Potlatch
    S.2572
  - Arkansas-Idaho Exchange: Background, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    H.R.5336; S.2572
  - Arkansas-Idaho Exchange: Funding Idaho Lands, 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    Arkansas--Public Lands; Idaho--Public Lands; Potlatch; Land and Water Conservation Fund; Bureau of Land Management; Wetlands; Coeur d'Alene Lake
    Bumpers, Dale; Craig, Larry E.; Reed, Scott
  - Arkansas-Idaho Exchange: Grandmother Mountain, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Arkansas--Public Lands; Idaho--Public Lands; Potlatch; Grandmother Mountain
  - Arkansas-Idaho Exchange: Hearings, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Arkansas--Public Lands; Idaho--Public Lands; Potlatch; Grandmother Mountain; Idaho Conservation League; Colorado-Public Lands; Salmon River
    Benson, Mark
    H.R.5336; H.R.3693; S.2101
  - Arkansas-Idaho Exchange: Larry LaRocco Statements, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Arkansas--Public Lands; Idaho--Public Lands
    Statement before Subcommittee on Public Lands, National Parks, and Forests 5/21/1992
  - Arkansas-Idaho Exchange: Press, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Arkansas-Idaho Exchange: University of Idaho-Forest Service Exch, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Arkansas--Public Lands; Idaho--Public Lands; Targhee National Forest; Kaniksu National Forest
    H.R.3693
  - Arms Control, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Nuclear Test Ban Treaty; Arms Control
  - Art Education, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Arts
  - Asia: Congressional Activities, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    International Trade; International Relations; Vietnam; China; Hong Kong
  - Associated Credit Bureaus, Inc., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Consumer Credit
  - Augmentation Awards, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Air Force Training Range
  - Aviation, 1991-1994 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    General Aviation Accident Liability Standards; Air Pilots; Airlines; General Aviation Revitalization Act; Department of Commerce
    H.R.3087
  - B-1B Bomber, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - B-2 Advanced Technology Bomber, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    B-2 Bomber
  - Balanced Budget, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Balanced Budget Amendment; Health Care Reform
    Panetta, Leon; Stenholm, Charles W.; Bork, Robert H.
    S.J.Res.298; H.J.Res.290
  - Balanced Budget Amendment, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Stenholm, Charles W.
    H.J.103
  - Balanced Budget Amendment, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Budget Deficits
    H.J.Res.103
  - Bank Sales of Mutual Funds, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Banks and Banking
  - Bank Sales of Mutual Funds, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Bank Study Group, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    Bank Examinations; Banks and Banking
    McDonough, William J.
  - Banking, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    Federal Deposit Insurance Act; Banks and Banking
    H.R.6; H.R.2094
  - Banking, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Banking Services, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Banks and Banking; Financial Services Access Act; Consumer Credit; Community Development
    H.R.1448; H.R.2350
  - Banking: CRS Reports, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Banks and Banking; Securities; Insurance Industry; Life Insurance; Taxation; Savings and Loan
  - Banking: Miscellaneous, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Banks and Banking; Insurance Industry
  - Banking: Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Banking: Regulatory Restructuring, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Federal Reserve System; Banks and Banking
    Fiechter, Jonathan L.
  - Bankrupt Carrier, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    Interstate Commerce Act; Transportation
  - Banks, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    Bank Insurance Fund; Banks and Banking
  - Barley Commission, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    International Trade
  - Base Closure Commission, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    Military Bases
  - Baseball, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Basques, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Bayview Naval Research Center, 1991-1993 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    Lake Pend Oreille
  - Beacon Inc., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    Beacon Technology; Department of Commerce
  - Benewah Soil and Water Conservation District, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    Land Use; Benewah County, Idaho
  - Birds of Prey: Archaeology, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    Snake River Birds of Prey National Conservation Area; Idaho--Petroglyphs
  - Birds of Prey: Area, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    Snake River Birds of Prey Natural Area; Military Land Reform and Reassessment, 1991; Grazing.
    H.R.236; H.R.2141; H.R.3564
  - Birds of Prey: Background, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    Snake River Birds of Prey National Conservation Area; Idaho Power Company
    H.R.2141
  - Birds of Prey: Cattle Association Letter, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    Snake River Birds of Prey National Conservation Area; Idaho Cattle Association; Grazing
    H.R.236
  - Birds of Prey: Changes, December 1992 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    Snake River Birds of Prey National Conservation Area
  - Birds of Prey: Committees/Co-Sponsors, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Birds of Prey: Compromise of 102nd, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Birds of Prey: Contacts, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Snake River Birds of Prey National Conservation Area; Sierra Club; World Center for Birds of Prey
  - Birds of Prey: Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Snake River Birds of Prey National Conservation Area; Raptor Research Foundation; Idaho--Constituent Communication
    Statement before Subcommittee on National Parks and Public Lands, 10/24/1991
  - Birds of Prey: Dear Colleague, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Birds of Prey: Deer Flat Refuge, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Snake River Birds of Prey National Conservation Area; Deer Flat Wildlife Refuge
  - Birds of Prey: Drafts of Bill, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Birds of Prey: Grazing, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Snake River Birds of Prey National Conservation Area; Grazing; Idaho Cattle Association; Owyhee Cattlemen's Association; Public Lands
  - Birds of Prey: Hearing, 1993 June 17 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Birds of Prey: House Floor Vote, 1991-1993 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Vento, Bruce F.
    Statement on Floor 11/23/1991; Statement on Floor 5/11/1993
  - Birds of Prey: Kaysville Bill, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Snake River Birds of Prey National Conservation Area; Kaysville, Utah
    S.1183
  - Birds of Prey: LaRocco Amendment, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Snake River Birds of Prey National Conservation Area; Mines and Mining
    Craig, Larry E.
    S.1183; H.R.2141
  - Birds of Prey: Mark-up, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Statement to Subcommittee on National Parks and Public Lands, 3/17/1993
  - Birds of Prey: Military, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    Snake River Birds of Prey National Conservation Area; Public Lands; Training Range; Idaho National Guard
  - Birds of Prey: Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Statement at Dedication of Snake River Birds of Prey National Conservation Area, 5/21/1994
  - Birds of Prey: National Conservation Areas, 1989-1991 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    H.R.2141; P.L.100-696
  - Birds of Prey: Plan, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Birds of Prey: Press/Articles, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Birds of Prey: Research Project, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    Snake River Birds of Prey National Conservation Area; Raptor Research Foundation; Idaho Army National Guard
  - Birds of Prey: Simplot, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    Snake River Birds of Prey National Conservation Area; J.R. Simplot Co.
    Andrus, Cecil D.
  - Birds of Prey: Slide Show, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Birds of Prey: Statements and Talking Points, 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    Snake River Birds of Prey National Conservation Area; Grazing
    Statement on Floor 5/11/1993, 4/30/1991, 11/23/1991, 8/12/1991; Statement to Subcommittee on National Parks and Public Lands 2/23/1993, 10/24/1991, 5/10/1994
    H.R.2141; H.R.236
  - Birds of Prey: Testimony Idaho, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    Snake River Birds of Prey National Conservation Area; Idaho--Congressional Hearings; Idaho Cattle Association
  - Birds of Prey: The Bill, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Birds of Prey: The Bill: Final and Report, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    Public Law 103-64
  - Birds of Prey: Washington, DC Testimony, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    Snake River Birds of Prey National Conservation Area; Sierra Club; Bureau Land Management; Idaho National Guard
    Stallings, Richard H.
  - Birds of Prey: Water, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    Snake River Birds of Prey National Conservation Area; Colorado Wilderness Act; Bureau of Land Management; Hagerman Fossil Bed
    Strong, Clive J.; Reed, Scott W.
  - Boeing Wind Tunnel Project, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    Rathdrum, Idaho
  - Boise Cascade, 1992-1994 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    Small Business Administration; International Trade
  - Boise National Forest, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    Forest Reserves; Forest Health
  - Bombing Range Expansion, 1989-1993 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    Bureau of Land Management; Mountain Home Air Force Base; Saylor Creek; Duck Valley Indian Reservation; Bombing Ranges--Environmental Aspects
  - Bombing Ranges, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    Military Land Reform and Reassessment Act; Bureau of Land Management
    H.R.4404; H.R.3564
  - Bombing Ranges, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    Mountain Home Air Force Base; Duck Valley Indian Reservation
  - Bonneville Power Administration, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Energy; Salmon
  - Bonneville Power Administration, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Columbia River--Dams; Snake River--Dams; Salmon
  - Bonneville Power Administration, 1992-1994 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Cascade Reservoir; Columbia River
  - Bonneville Power Administration, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Salmon; Lower Granite Dam; Army Corps of Engineers; Steelhead
  - Bonneville Power Administration, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Salmon; Snake River; Columbia River; Barge Transportation
  - Bonneville Power Administration, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Columbia River; Water Resources; Dams; Salmon
  - Bonneville Power Administration, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Bonneville Power Administration, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Salmon; Snake River; Hydroelectric Power
    DeFazio, Peter
  - Bonneville Power Administration: Energy, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Bonneville Power Administration: Rate Increase, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Bosnia, 1991-1994 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Yugoslavia
  - Bovine Growth Hormones, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    National Dairy Promotion and Research Board; Idaho Dairymen's Association; Food and Drug Administration
    Espy, Mike
  - Brady Bill, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Gun Control; Crime Prevention; Hunting
    H.R.1025; H.R.1815
  - Brady Bill, 1991-1994 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Gun Control
    H.R.7; H.R. 1412
  - Breast Cancer Awareness Month, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Broadcasting, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    Information Networks; Cable Television
  - Broadcasting Site Fees, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    Communication Sites; Idaho Communications Ltd. Partnership; Bureau of Land Management; Land Use--Fees
    H.R.1686
  - Broadcasting Site Fees, 1992-1994 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    Bureau of Land Management; Public Lands--Fees; Communication Towers
  - Broadcasting Site Fees, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    Communication Sites; Bureau of Land Management; Land Use--Fees
  - Broadcasting Site Fees, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    Communication Sites; National Association of Broadcasters; Bureau of Land Management; Land Use--Fees
    H.R.3657
  - Broadcasting Site Fees, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    Communication Sites; Forest Service; Land Use--Fees
  - Broadcasting Sites, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    Communication Sites; Television; Radio Broadcasts; Public Lands; Bureau of Land Management
    Brownell, Mark
  - Brokered Deposits, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    Federal Deposit Security Act; Securities
    H.R.4415
  - Bryden Canyon Road Project, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    Lewiston, Idaho; Idaho--Roads; Department of Commerce
  - Budget and Tax Proposals, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    Agriculture--Budgets; Entitlements; Budgets
  - Budget Committee, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Medicare
    Gradison, Willis
  - Budget Position, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Budget: Idaho, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Budgets; Interest Rates
  - Budget: Low Interest Rates, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 4)